mojostreet.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy | Mojostreet.com

Mojostreet Infomedia Services Pvt. Ltd. (“ _Mojostreet_ ,” “we,” or “us”) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared. This Privacy Policy explains what information of yours will be collected by _Mojostreet_ when you use the _Mojostreet_ Service. Additionally, it explains how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of such information. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect by other means (including offline) or from other sources. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this policy are defined in our Terms of Use. Our expectation is that _Mojostreet_ Users will use this service for harmless social purposes. We would like to extend a cautionary note however, that by its nature, your location information may be subject to misuse and over-monitoring by others including your friends, family, or acquaintances. We therefore request you to manage your own mobile and profile privacy preferences on the service on a periodic basis.

**What Information Is Collected?**  

> Mojostreet will store the information that you provide to us during the registration process as well as during the use of the Service. This information may include but is not limited to your email address, name, picture, phone number, and/ or Facebook/Twitter login ids as well as non identifying information like gender, Birthday etc. While using the service, you may choose to share more information such as locations and tips, photos which may be publicly displayed to other Users and third party sites or services depending on your privacy and opt-in settings. Mojostreet automatically receives information about your location when you use the service. This device information is used for improving the content of the service, customizing the advertizing on the Service and communicating with you about offers and discounts. 
> 
> We will also collect the email, phone numbers, FB IDs of your friends when you use our mobile applications in a safe and encrypted format. This information is used for the sole purpose of helping your build your network on Mojostreet and also help your find your friends. 
> 
> We also automatically collect certain information when you use Mojostreet, such as your location/GPS coordinates (if you enable this feature), a device identifier (but not the UDID), MAC address, Internet Protocol (IP) address (if using a browser), operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring site and your activity on Mojostreet.
> 
> We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of "cookies”. These are small files that your browser places on your computer. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our services, and to improve our services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

**How Is My Information Protected?**  
_Mojostreet_ uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. However, _Mojostreet_ cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

Your _Mojostreet_ account personal information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You can prevent unauthorized access to your account and personal information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

**How Is My Information Shared?**  

> **Sharing with friends**  
>  Your “friends” see the location and time of each of your check-ins, tips and photos (that you leave there), presidentships. While your friends will be able to see the time of your check-ins, other users will only be shown the date of the check-in. Individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge. Hence we urge you to exercise caution while adding a user as a “friend”.
> 
> **Sharing with everyone**  
>  Information such as your name and picture, social network links, presidentships, list of friends, tips, photos are shared by default with the _Mojostreet_ community. However, you can choose to restrict the visibility of your check-in related information to your friends only. 
> 
> **Sharing with partners and authorities**  
>  _Mojostreet_ works closely with its partners in order to provide discounts and other offers to you through _Mojostreet_ ’s service. Mojostreet may choose to share your personal information with its partners for the potential benefit of customers.  
>  We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that it is necessary in order to comply with the law of the land, to enforce our terms of use or to protect the rights, property, or safety of _Mojostreet_ , our employees, our users, or others.

**Your Choices About Your Information**  
You have the right to decline to submit personally identifiable information through the service. If you choose to do so, _Mojostreet_ may not be able to provide certain services to you. You may update or correct your account information [and email preferences] at any time by logging in to your account. Currently your check-ins have two privacy settings. **By default, check-ins are shared with everyone**. You may choose to share a check-in with only your friends at the time of check-in and bypass the default setting.

**How Is Information Removed From My Account?**  
Even after you remove information from your account or profile, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere, to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users.

**Tracking**  
Mojostreet uses Google Analytics to better understand who is using the Service, and how it is being used. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect and store anonymous information such as the time(s) of visit, pages visited, time spent on each page of the website, IP address, and type of operating system used. We use this information to improve the Service and make it appealing to as many users as possible.

**Links**  
You may come across links to external websites on _Mojostreet_. We are not responsible for the practices employed by these websites. This privacy policy governs only the practices collected on our service.

**Will There Be Changes To This Privacy Policy?**    
Mojostreet may amend this Privacy Policy periodically. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our _Service_ or by sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use the Service after such changes have been first posted.

**What If I Have Questions Or Concerns?**  If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy while using the Service, please send a detailed message to:  **[privacy@mojostreet.com](mailto:privacy@mojostreet.com)**. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
